[
  {
    "question": "Who is the first executive president of Nigeria?",
    "choice1": "Chief Obafemi Awolowo",
    "choice2": "Dr. Nnamdi Azikwe",
    "choice3": "Sheu Shagari",
    "choice4": "Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
    "answer": 3
  },

{"question": "Who was the first Millitary Head of State in  Nigeria?",
    "choice1": "General Yakubu Gowon",
    "choice2": "General Aguiyi Ironsi",
    "choice3": "Major General Muritala Muhammed",
    "choice4": "General Olusegun Obasanjo",
    "answer": 2
  },

{"question": "A system in which no single person serves as the chief executive is known as?",
    "choice1": "Republican",
    "choice2": "Revolutionary",
    "choice3": "Collegial",
    "choice4": "Parliamentary",
    "answer": 4
  },

{"question": "A system in which power is derived from control over land is called?",
    "choice1": "Oligarchy",
    "choice2": "Feudalism",
    "choice3": "Socialism",
    "choice4": "Welfarism",
    "answer": 2
},
  
{"question": "Who is the Richest Man in Africa?",
  "choice1": "Mike Otedola",
  "choice2": "Oprah Winfrey",
  "choice3": "Adebanjo Israel",
  "choice4": "Aliko Dangote",
  "answer": 4
},

{"question": "Who is the first Millitary President of Nigeria?",
  "choice1": "General Ibrahim Babaginda",
  "choice2": "General Tunde Idiagbon",
  "choice3": "Major General Phillip Effiong",
  "choice4": "General Adbulsalam Abubakar",
  "answer": 1
},

{"question": "Who is the current NAFDAC Director-General?",
  "choice1": "Mrs. Okonjo Iwela",
  "choice2": "Mojisola Christianah Adeyeye",
  "choice3": "Mahmood Yakubu",
  "choice4": "AIsha Adamu",
  "answer": 2
},

{"question": "Who is the Secretary General of the United Nations?",
  "choice1": "Antonio Gutteres",
  "choice2": "Kim Park",
  "choice3": "Richard Edward",
  "choice4": "Peter Oni",
  "answer": 1
},


{"question": "Which state is the major producer of Coal in Nigeria?",
  "choice1": "Osun State",
  "choice2": "Enugu State",
  "choice3": "Akwa Ibom",
  "choice4": "Zamfara State",
  "answer": 2
},


{"question": "Nigera is divided into how many geopolitical zones?",
  "choice1": "8",
  "choice2": "7",
  "choice3": "6",
  "choice4": "5",
  "answer": 3
}


]
